<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="index.xsl"?>
<catalog>
  <cd>
    <topic>5 Reasons To Apply For Medical Loan</topic>
    <date>January 04, 2021</date>
    <content>Emergencies are rare, but they are always unexpected.  When you are faced with a tough situation, you may need funds quickly. When you face a medical emergency, the last thing you want is to file paperwork to raise funds. APMK Bank Personal Loans are quick and hassle-free. Pre-approved customers don’t need any documentation and for other customers the documentation is minimal.</content>
  </cd>
  <cd>
    <topic>Store Banking Passwords Safely</topic>
    <date>December 07, 2020</date>
    <content>In recent times, both internet and personal banking have caught on quite rapidly, with many people opting to bank online or over the phone. Since your bank accounts are the gateways to your finances, it is extremely important to keep them safe from unauthorised access.</content>
  </cd>
  <cd>
    <topic>Travel Checklist</topic>
    <date>December 09, 2020</date>
    <content>Seasoned travellers prefer carrying Forex Cards rather than currency notes for the sake of safety. An excellent option is the APMK Bank ForexPlus Card that allow easy online currency management in foreign countries. There are different types of cards you can choose from, based on your requirements. You can even transfer the balance on the card from one currency to another while travelling across borders for additional flexibility.</content>
  </cd>
  <cd>
    <topic>Save Tax With Mutual Funds</topic>
    <date>December 12, 2020</date>
    <content>Mutual funds, also known as Equity Linked Savings Scheme (ELSS), are great tax-saving instruments under Section 80C of the Income Tax Act, 1961. This section allows you to claim benefits from your taxable income if you put your money into certain investments.</content>
  </cd>
  <cd>
    <topic>Benefits Of Personal Loan To Repay Debt</topic>
    <date>December 18, 2020</date>
    <content>Personal Loans are one of the best products offered by banks. They are often unsecured in nature i.e. you do not have to provide any collateral against the loan. The loan amount is typically sanctioned and disbursed in a just a couple of days.</content>
  </cd>
  <cd>
    <topic>Understanding Mobile Banking</topic>
    <date>December 14, 2020</date>
    <content>With the popularity of online banking and the growing use of mobile web browsing, Mobile Banking is becoming an everyday task for most people. More so, because it’s convenient, easy and can be accessed on the go. But what is Mobile Banking? Simply put, Mobile Banking is the use of financial services over mobile devices such as cellular phones.</content>
  </cd>
</catalog>